Sergio Campos

1110 Barberry Dr Taylorsville UT, 84123 8016710445 Scam81494@gmail.com

PROFILE

A fast learner who was born into retail, started working at age ten at family business providing him with a strong work ethic and customer service skills. 5+ years of retail experience outside the family business often recognized for taking the lead in stressful situations, jumping head first into all areas of the business whenever it's needed, adapting to new policy's quickly and ensuring that both new and experienced employees are up to date on company policy.

EXPERIENCE

O/N Assistant Manager, Walmart; West Jordan, UT = 2019 = 2020

Manage overnight team, hire new associates, make schedules. Ensure all freight is stocked and binned away and that the store is presentable in the morning. Perform safety checks on all power equipment, and plan out module resets for the store.

Fresh Cap 2 Support, Walmart; Midvale, UT = 2019 - 2019

Lead a team of 5, ensure all fresh areas such as; bakery, deli, produce, meat are well stocked, clean, and free of any of any non fresh products. Perform markdowns, donate products about to go out of date. Sweep out coolers, wash floors in ambient rooms, take out trash and ensure all food waste is disposed of properly

Dairy/Frozen Department Manager, Walmart; Midvale, UT = 2018 - 2019

Keep Dairy and Frozen sections clean, shelves full, pull out of dates, keep fridges organized. Order merchandise and set up displays, manage associates working in the areas

Cap 2 Supervisor, Walmart; Midvale, UT = 2018-2018

Manage a team of two - ten unloaders, unload all trucks as fast as possible, make sure consumables gets stock, keep track of all high ticket items and make sure they get locked up, sweep out trailers and load it with anything that needs to be sent back to the distribution center, stage fright and leave backroom clean ready for overnight shift.

O/N Stocker, Walmart; Midvale, UT = 2017-2018

Stock freight, bin merchandise, clean up area, zone.

EDUCATION

East High, Salt Lake City UT — GED

SKILLS

Speaks fluent Spanish, problem solving, customer service, flexibility, leadership.